Mikołaj Zabiegliński

Junior data specialist

I am a data analyst and an aerospace engineer. I am currently employed as a junior specialist in a credit risk analysis database. I analyse data and test and implement processes. I know technologies and environments used in data analysis. I am fluent in English.

EXPERIENCE

$PKO\ BP,\ {\rm Warsaw}\ -\ Junior\ specialist$

February 2023-

- Junior specialist in Data Risk Information Team
- Designing, testing, implementing, adopting and maintaining data processing processes
- Overseeing data flows
- Maintenance and support of the data analysis infrastructure
- Automating internal administration processes
- SAS, SQL, Python, bash, Git, Jira, GCP

PKO BP, Warsaw – Intern

August 2023-February 2023

- Intern in Data Risk Information Team
- Supporting the team in process implementation
- Designing data processing processes

Evionica, Warsaw - Engineer

January 2020-April 2022

- Technical aerospace knowledge specialist
- Design and verification of manuals and training related to usage and aircraft pilotage
- Agile framework

CONTACT

- ☑ mikolaj.zabieglinski@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/mikołaj-zabiegliński-4bba88238/
- https://github.com/m-zabieglinski/
- **** +48 795 965 432

EDUCATION

MSc - Data Analysis Warsaw School of Economics October 2021-

BSc - Aerospace Engineering Warsaw University of Technology October 2016-March 2021

CODING LANGUAGES

Python SQL SAS 4GL

PL-SQL bash R

TECHNOLOGIES

Linux Git Jira

SAS MS SQL GCP AWS

SOFT SKILLS

Agile framework Teamwork

Communication Individual work

LANGUAGES

English - C2 - CAE certificate

Polish - native

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

Mathematics

Tabletop games